<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Sorcery" Logo="https://i.postimg.cc/fRBSLWsQ/sorcery-a19-logo-v09.png" Description="Play 7 Days to Die as a balanced post apocalyptic zombie vanquishing Sorcerer. Through training and discovery, you'll learn how to deport the undead straight back to hell by casting elemental spells of Fire, Ice and Lightning.">
			<Server Name="Sorcery" Logo="https://i.postimg.cc/fRBSLWsQ/sorcery-a19-logo-v09.png">
			<Description>Sorcery Staves and Rebalance (v0.96) - Completely Redesigned for A19!
http://www.SorceryMod.com
Play 7 Days to Die as a balanced post apocalyptic zombie vanquishing Sorcerer. Through training and discovery, you'll learn how to deport the undead straight back to hell by casting elemental spells of Fire, Ice and Lightning.
• Vanilla game 100% untouched, add-only policy!
• Balanced around vanilla gameplay, you must train to gain and sustain your power!
• Unique animations, art, effects and sounds for spells and items
• New Spells: Craft, Master and Upgrade 5 Spells per element!
• New Enemies: Wisps, Touched, Fallen (Champion), Awakened (Boss), Ancient (Raid)
• New Attributes: Sorcery, Fire, Ice, Lightning, Unholy, Holy
• New Resource: Spirit (mana required to perform all Sorcery)
• New Dual Skill Tree and Perks: Arcane, Fire, Ice, Lightning
• New Crafting: Armor, Weapons, Mods, Spells, Potions, Scrolls, Stations, Blocks, Resources
• New Armor Sets: Arcane, Fire, Ice, Lightning
• New Masteries: Alchemy, Runesmithing, Spirit, Essence, Arcane, Fire, Ice, Lightning
• New Weapon Types: Magic Staves, Spellcasts, Spell Turrets
• New Traps: Spell Turrets, Elemental Traps
• New Mods: Rare, Legendary and Class Runes
• New Quests: Sorcery storyline and ocean of new Quests!
• Play-style: Sorcerer (Spellcaster)
• Play-style: Alchemist (Potions, Bombs)
• Play-style: Archer Mage (Spell Arrows) 
• Play-style: Gun Mage (Spell Ammo)
• Play-style: Melee Mage (Spell Weapons)
• Weapon Abilities: Primary, Secondary, Passive and Charge abilities
• Rune Mods: Harness the power of Runes to augment your weapons, armor and gear!
• Alchemy: Craft Potions, Elixirs and Bombs
• Sexy Loot: Item Sets, Armor, Weapons, Mods, Spells, Potions, Scrolls and more!

Next Public Release: September TBD (Lightning Element)
SUPPORTER ACCESS: Become a Supporter to gain full-feature testing access, unlock the Treasury Perks and help ensure ongoing development!

HOME: http://www.SorceryMod.com
DISCORD: http://discord.SorceryMod.com
FORUM: http://forum.SorceryMod.com
WIKI: http://wiki.SorceryMod.com
DIFFICULTY MODES: http://modes.SorceryMod.com

FULLY COMPATIBLE: DARKNESS FALLS (v3.x): Sorcery is fully compatible with Darkness Falls! (must remove Deep Pockets from Mods)
DF + Sorcery Instructions: https://discord.gg/EnHrDDd
DF Compatibility Patch: http://df-download.sorcerymod.com/
			</Description>
			<DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>http://forum.SorceryMod.com</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
			<Download>https://github.com/7d2d-sorcery/Sorcery</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
