<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Sorcery" Logo="https://i.postimg.cc/s221WC7s/sorcery-logo-splash.png" Description="Play 7 Days to Die as a balanced post apocalyptic zombie vanquishing Sorcerer. Through training and discovery, you'll learn how to deport the undead straight back to hell by casting elemental spells of Fire, Ice and Lightning.">
			<Server Name="Sorcery" Logo="https://i.postimg.cc/s221WC7s/sorcery-logo-splash.png">
			<Description>Sorcery v0.76 - Lightning + Balance!
http://www.SorceryMod.com

Play 7 Days to Die as a balanced post apocalyptic zombie vanquishing Sorcerer. Through training and discovery, you'll learn how to deport the undead straight back to hell by casting elemental spells of Fire, Ice and Lightning.
- Unique animations, art, effects and sounds for spells and items
- Pure Spellcaster playstyle
- Spellcrafting: 5 unique abilities for each unique spell
- Armor Crafting: Craft Fire and Ice Armor via Conjure
- Rune Crafting: Craft Fire and Ice Rune Mods via Conjure
- Spell Weapon Abilities: primary, secondary, passive, charge
- Sorcery Crafting Conjures: feed rituals with Essence
- New Attribute: Sorcery
- New Dual Skill Tree and Perks
- Fire, Ice, Lightning Mastery: learn how to craft and augment spells
- Spellcast Mastery: primary, secondary, passive and charge abilities
- Rune Mastery: harness the power of Runes to augment your spells
- Essence Mastery: demystify and awaken the elemental essence of the world to extract and craft spells and weapons with essence.
- Fire, Ice, Lightning Spells: upgrade each spell with five alterations

Latest Version: 0.76 - Lightning + Balance!
HOME: http://www.SorceryMod.com
DISCORD: http://discord.SorceryMod.com
FORUM: http://forum.SorceryMod.com
WIKI: http://wiki.SorceryMod.com

**COMPATIBLE** DARKNESS FALLS (2.1+): Sorcery Modlet version is fully compatible with Darkness Falls (17.3 / latest). Under Darkness Falls Install: Manage Modlets &gt; Download Sorcery &gt; Ready to play!

**COMPATIBLE** RAVENHEARST (5.1+): Sorcery Modlet version is fully compatible with Ravenhearst (5.1). Under Ravenhearst Install: Manage Modlets &gt; Download Sorcery &gt; Open and Copy Sorcery Localization.txt contents and paste the copied Localization text into the Ravenhearst Localization.txt (at the very end, new line) &gt; Ready to play!  More Info: https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?109145-Sorcery&amp;p=963640&amp;viewfull=1#post963640

**NOTE** This version of Sorcery is NOT EAC safe; You must play with EAC disabled. The pure XML Modlet version of Sorcery may be used with EAC enabled: https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?109145-Sorcery
			</Description>
			<DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>http://forum.SorceryMod.com</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
			<Download>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/7D2DMods/Profiles/master/LocalizationProfile.txt</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>